Guide to the Actors' Fund of America Records WAG.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series V: Fundraising Activities, 1886-2002
  - Subseries V:B: Benefits and Fairs, 1886-2002.
    - Night of 100 Stars: Roger and Cowan Inc., Publicity, Feb 14, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Evite, Apr 18, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Dream Girls, Jun 27, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Nine, Sep 12, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Cats, Oct 5, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - 42nd Street, Nov 1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Cats, Feb 6, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Parade of Stars, May 2, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - You Can’t Take It with You, Jul 17, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Dream Girls, Aug 29, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Brighton Beach Memories, Oct 30, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - La Cage Aux Folles, Nov 6, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - On Your Toes, Nov 20, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Torch Song Trilogy, Jan 23, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Rink, Jun 24, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Hurly Burly, Sep 23, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Harrigan ‘n Hart, Jan 31, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Night of 100 Stars II, Feb 17, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Night of 100 Stars II: Clippings, Feb 17, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Night of 100 Stars II: Dinner, Feb 17, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Night of 100 Stars II: Roger & Cowen Inc, Publicity, Feb 17, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Night of 100 Stars II: Thank You Ad, Feb 17, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Night of Unsung Stars, Jun 3, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Biloxi Blues, Jun 23, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Best of the Best, Nov 3, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Only the Best Gala, Macy’s, Nov 13, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Bridge to Broadway (Harms Plaza Theatre), Nov 18, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Chorus Line, Movie Premiere, Dec 9, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Chorus Line, Movie Premiere: Press, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Shear Madness, Apr 1, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - L.A. Stage Company Special Event, Jun 16, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Legends, Jul 1986 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Liberty State Park, NJ: Liberty Week, Jul 1986 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Producers Guild: New York International Film and Festival Awards Benefit, Nov 1, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Ginger Man Event, Dec 18, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Break A Leg Award Presentation, Jun 13, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Show, Jun 13, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday), Jun 22, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday): Publicity, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Career Transition for Dancers: Art Gala and Auction, Sep 21, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Starlight Express, Sep 23, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Capital Salute to the Entertainment World, Oct 5, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Shear Madness, Nov 5, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - For Me and My Girl, Jan 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 12, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Christmas Carol: Clippings, Dec 12, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Carol: Correspondence, Dec 12, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Christmas Carol: Correspondence, Thank You Notes, Dec 1988 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitations, Dec 12, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitations, Corporate, Dec 12, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Christmas Carol: Planning, Dec 12, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Carol: Publicity, Dec 12, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Jerome Robbins’ Broadway, Mar 27, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Dennis Collado’s Fund Raiser, May 1989-Jun 1989 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Phantom of the Opera, Aug 27, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Takarazuka, Oct 25, 1989-Oct 29, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 11, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Christmas Carol: Program (signed), Dec 11, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Advertisement, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Artiste and Craft Guilds Committee, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Celebrities, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Correspondence, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Correspondence, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Diamond Information Center, Promotion, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Dinners and Parties, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Executive Committee, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: IATSE Boycott, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Invitation, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Planning, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Play Bill, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Play Bill, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Press Clippings, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Press Clippings (II), May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Press Kit, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Performance Schedules, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Raffle (Noel Coward’s Mercedes), May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Reports, Profits, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Sales, May 5, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Script, May 5, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Night of 100 Stars III: Stewart, Jimmy, May 5, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Chorus Lin e: Press Kit, Mar 31, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Phantom of the Opera, Jan 21, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - City of Angels, Feb 17, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Les Miserables, Apr 3, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Candida, Apr 7, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Six Degrees of Separation, Apr 28, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Lost in Yonkers, Jun 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Phantom of the Opera, Jun 17, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Madame Butterfly, Sep 8, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Phantom of the Opera, Sep 22, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Sara fina!, Sep 22, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Miss Saigon, Sep 27, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Nick and Nora, Oct 8, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Secret Garden, Oct 13, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Bon Appetit, Nov 11, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 10, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Christmas Carol: Correspondence, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Christmas Carol: Dinner, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitation and Contributions Lists, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitation Ideas, Artwork, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Christmas Carol: Planning, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Christmas Carol: Playbill, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Christmas Carol: Publicity, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Christmas Carol: Script, Dec 16, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Christmas Carol, Dec 19, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Most Happy Fella, Apr 12, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - CATS, Apr 19, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Bernard Jacobs’ Speech, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Celebrities, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Commemorative Advertisements, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Contributions, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Correspondence, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Correspondence, “Cannot Attend”, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Finances, Account Memos, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Guest List, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Invitation, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Mailing Lists, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Memorandum, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Program and Arrangements, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Salute to Entertainment: Reports, Jun 15, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Christmas Carol: Correspondence, Dec 15, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Christmas Carol: Finances, Dec 15, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Christmas Carol: Invitation, Dec 15, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Christmas Carol: Publicity, Dec 15, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Christmas Carol: Reception, Dec 15, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Christmas Carol: Reports, Dec 15, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Feb 26, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - For the Love of the Dove, Jun 17, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Magic and Music: Gala, Dec 16, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Stay Home: Gala, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Feb 24, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Lucille Lortel Awards, May 5, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - The Gin Game (Box 24, Folder 12a)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Mar 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Mr. Smith Goes to the Plaza: Gala, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Mar 12, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Nothing like a Dame, Mar 18, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Standing Ovation (James M. Nederlander 80th Birthday Celebration), Apr 29, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Nightingale: Poster, undated (Box 24, Folder 17a)
    - Fundraising Updates, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Cancelled Performances, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Subseries V:C: Bread Basket Campaigns, 1938-1980.
    - Abbott, George (Bread Basket Chairman), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Act I, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Actors’ Equity Association, 1968-1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - American Conservatory Theatre, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - American Shakespeare Festival, 1965-1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - American Stage Festival, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Association of Theatrical Press Agents and Managers, 1968, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Barnstormers (Tamworth, NH), 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Berkshire Theatre Festival, 1972-1979 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Beverly Dinner Playhouse, 1974-1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Blood Donor Drive, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1963-1968 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Brunswick Music Theater, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Burstyn, Ellen and Grodin, Charles (Bread Basket Co-Chairmen), 1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Candlelight Dinner Playhouse, 1965-1967, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Cape Cod Melody Tent, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Cecilwood Theatre, 1966-1980 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Chanhassen Dinner Theatre, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Chicago: Actors’ Fund Week, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Collectors, undated, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Corning Summer Theater, 1965-1980 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1951; 1965, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Actors’ Equity, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Dinner Theaters, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Eisenhower Theatre, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Elitch Gardens Theater, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Forrest Theatre, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Gish, Lillian: Luncheon, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Gracie Mansion Reception, 1963-1979 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival, 1965-1980 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Grendel’s Lair Cabaret Theater, 1978-1980 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Guber, Lee, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Harmon, Charlotte, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Hayloft Dinner Theatre, Nov 1978 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Hepburn, Katherine (Chairman, Winter Bread Basket Drive), 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Hippodrome Theatre, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Individual Contributors, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Individual Contributors, 1978-1980 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Information Sheet on Breadbasket Drives, undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Ivorytown Playhouse, 1965-1972, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - John Golden Fund, 1959-1962, 1965-1975 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - John Drew Theater, 1966-1979 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Kaye, Danny, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Keeler, Ruby (Bread Basket Chairman), 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Kenley Papers, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Lakes Region Playhouse (Gilford, NH), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Lakewood Theater (Skowhegan, ME), 1965-1972, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - League of New York Theatres and Producers, 1969-1980 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Little Theater on the Square, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Little Theater on the Square: Programs, 1968-1971, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Master Theatre Lists, 1968, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Melody Top Theater, 1966-1980 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Merit Awards, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Music Box Theatre, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - New Bolton Hill Dinner Theatre, Oct 1978 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - New Jersey Shakespeare Festival, 1972-1976, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - New Mechanic Theatre, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Nichols, Mike (Bread Basket Chairman), 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Off-Broadway Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1965-1979 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Orpheum Theater, Dec 1978 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Out-of-Town Theatre, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Pantages Theatre, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Paramount Arts Centre, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Peterborough Players, 1964-1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, 1965-1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Preston, Robert (Bread Basket Chairman), 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Procedures, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Program Inserts, 1963-1972, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Program Inserts Distribution Lists, 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Publicity, 1966-1968, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Publicity Expenses, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Pub Theatrical, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - R. Greenspan and Co., Inc (Clipper Industries), 1965-1970 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Reeves, John, 1965-1966, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Reports, undated, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Report, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Reports, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Reynolds, Debbie (Chairman), 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Road Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Road Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1968-1975 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Road Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1980-1980 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Road Theatres: Collection Sheets, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Sacramento Music Circus, 1965-1980 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Sebastian Dinner Theater, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Shady Grove Music Fair, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Sharon Playhouse, 1965-1970, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Shubert Theaters: Holiday Matinee Schedules, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Simon, Neil (Bread Basket Chairman), 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Smithville Theatre, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Southbury Playhouse, 1966-1980 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Speeches, 1965-1969, 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Star Musicals of Flint, Jul 1978 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Summer Bread Basket, 1966, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Summer Bread Basket, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Summer Bread Basket, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Summer Bread Basket, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Summer Bread Basket: Dinner Collections, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Summer Bread Basket: Expenses, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Summer Bread Basket: Form Letters, 1965-1973 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Summer Bread Basket: Herald Distribution, undated, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Summer Bread Basket: Reports, 1965-1974 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Summer Bread Basket: Tallies, 1938, 1958-1977 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Theatre by the Sea, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Totem Pole Playhouse, Jul 1978 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Town and Country Playhouse, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Ushers’ Union, Information for, undated, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Village Dinner Theater, Jan 1981 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Westbury Music Fair, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Westport Country Playhouse, 1970-1971, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Wilbur Theatre, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Williamstown Theater, 1965-1967, 1970-1980 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Winter Bread Basket, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Winter Bread Basket, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Winter Bread Basket: Form Letters, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Winter Bread Basket: New York Theatres, 1966-1975 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Winter Bread Basket: Publicity, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Winter Bread Basket: Publicity, 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Winter Bread Basket: Road Theatres, 1964-1971 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Winter Bread Basket: Road Theatres, 1972-1977 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Winter Bread Basket: Speakers Assignments, 1965-1974 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Winter Bread Basket: Speakers, 1965-1974 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Winter Bread Basket: Tallies, 1964-1972 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Wolfboro Playhouse, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Subseries V:D: Benefits, Clippings Scrapbooks, 1934-1968.
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, Jan 1939-May 1939 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, Jul 1939-Dec 1939 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, Jan 1940-Apr 1940 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, May 1940-Nov 1940 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, Jan 1940-Jun 1941 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, Oct 1940-Dec 1941 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, Jan 1940-Mar 1942 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, Apr 1940-Nov 1942 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Benefits: Clipping Scrapbook, 1961-1968 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Series VI: Catholic Actors Guild Records, 1924-1980
  - Anniversary, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary (50th): Plaque Face, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 2a)
  - Award Presentations, 1970-1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Benefit, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Call Board, 1964-1972 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Call Board, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Call Board, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Call Board, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Call Board, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Cardinal Spelliman: To George Buck; St Genesius Medal, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 9a)
  - Communion Breakfast, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Cohan, George M.: Clippings, 1940-1961 (Box 28, Folder 10A)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Dinner-Dance, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Dinner-Dance, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Dinner-Dance, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Dinner-Dance, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Dinner-Dance: Archbishop Fulton J. Sheen Tributes, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Dinner-Dance: Entertainment, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Dinner-Dance: Florence Henderson, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Dinner-Dance: Florence Henderson Tributes, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Dinner-Dance: Gifts and Prizes, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Dinner-Dance: Prizes, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Dinner-Dance: Souvenir Signatures, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Dinner-Dance: Souvenir Signatures, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Executive Board, 1973, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Finances, 1943, 1967-1979 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Membership Figures, 1938-1970 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Most Holy Father (framed and signed by unidentified individual), undated (Box 40)
  - Papal Certificate, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Reverand John Talbot: Award from Columbian Assembly of New York, 1909 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Series VII: Rathbone Family Papers, 1903-1974
  - Being and Doing and Character and Conduct, Books with Inscription from Parent, 1906-1907 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: Rathbone, Basil, undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Rathbone, Basil, 1913, 1920-1945 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Rathbone, Basil, 1950-1967 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: Rathbone, Cynthia (from Basil), undated, 1940-1953 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: Rathbone, Ouida, undated, 1942-1974 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Rathbone, Ouida (from Basil), undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: Rathbone, Ouida (from Basil), 1926-1928, 1941-1967 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Rathbone, Ouida: Publishing, 1963-1968, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Estate of Basil Rathbone, undated, 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Family History, undated, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Letters from an Uitlanderer, Book Reviews, 1903 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Literary Material Recorded and Considered, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Rathbone, Basil: Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Rathbone, Basil: In and Out of Character, Galley Proofs, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Rathbone, Basil: In and Out of Character, Page Proofs, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Rathbone, Ouida: “Cynthia Rathbone Story,” Draft, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Rathbone, Ouida: “Happy Weddings,” Manuscript, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Rathbone, Ouida: Manuscript (I), undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Rathbone, Ouida: Manuscript (II), undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Rathbone, Ouida: Manuscript (III), undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Rathbone, Ouida: Manuscript (IV), undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Rathbone, Ouida: Manuscript (V), undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Rathbone, Ouida: Manuscript (VI), undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Series VIII: Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers Records, 1959-1980
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1964-1966 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board: Minutes, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)